<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>project analysis on Haruaki TAMADA</title>
    <link>https://tamada.github.io/tags/project-analysis/</link>
    <description>Recent content in project analysis on Haruaki TAMADA</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tamada.github.io/tags/project-analysis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Development support bot</title>
      <link>https://tamada.github.io/research/development_support_bot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tamada.github.io/research/development_support_bot/</guid>
      <description>:speaking_head: Overview This research topic aims to build a helpful bot for the software development. Also, the topic focuses on the bot on the Social Coding Platform in the social network services. The one goal of the topic is to build a bot for gently helping GitHub flow.
:books: Publications 宮崎 光，玉田 春昭，CUIツールの開発支援サービスとしての再構築手順の提案”，信学技法，Vol.119，No.246, SS2019-14, pp.7–12, October 2019（熊本）. 玉田 春昭，”初学者向けGitHub flow学習支援”，ソフトウェアシンポジウム2019 ワークショップ 討論テーマ（2）実証的ソフトウェア工学によるプログラミング教育とソフトウェア工学教育，August 2019.（東京） Ko Miyazaki, Haruaki Tamada, “Identifying Users in the Bridging Service between Two Different Chat Services using User Icons,” In Proc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project as a City</title>
      <link>https://tamada.github.io/research/project_as_a_city/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tamada.github.io/research/project_as_a_city/</guid>
      <description>:speaking_head: Overview Social coding platforms (SCPs) have realized spontaneous software evolution, where new source code and ideas are spontaneously proposed by altruistic developers. Although there are many projects operated by active communities performing spontaneous evolution, it is yet unclear that how such successful projects and communities have been formed and governed. In this paper, we propose a method that can investigate the history of every project in the SCP. Introducing the concept of project as a city, we consider every project in the SCP as a city, where a government and citizens develop a city through collaborative activities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Characteristics of the developers</title>
      <link>https://tamada.github.io/research/characteristics_of_developers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tamada.github.io/research/characteristics_of_developers/</guid>
      <description>:speaking_head: Overview In software development, multiple developers compose a team, and perform a development process. To succeed the development, understanding developers&amp;rsquo; characteristics are needed. However, there is no way to measure the characteristics of the developer by quantitative analysis. Therefore, a project manager often assigns team members based on his/her own sense, considering experience year of them.
This paper proposes a measurement framework for developers&amp;rsquo; characteristics using quantitative historical data. The proposed framework is useful for measuring developers&amp;rsquo; characteristics and building a team based on quantitative analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Applications of software birthmarks</title>
      <link>https://tamada.github.io/research/birthmark_applications/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tamada.github.io/research/birthmark_applications/</guid>
      <description>:speaking_head: Overview This research topics shows applications of software birthmarks. In our publications, we try to classify the programs using extracted software birthmarks. Because, we believe that the birthmarks shows the functionalities of the programs.
:books: Publications 牛窓 朋義, 門田 暁人, 玉田 春昭, 松本 健一, “使用クラスに基づくソフトウェアの機能面からの分類”, 信学技報 ソフトウェアサイエンス研究会, Vol.SS2009-17, pp.31-36, August 2009. 玉田 春昭，森崎 修司，門田 暁人，松本 健一，”バースマークを用いたソフトウェア拡張開発での流用度合いの測定”，情報処理学会第70回全国大会，pp.5-399-400, March 2008. Takesi Kakimoto, Akito Monden, Yasutaka Kamei, Haruaki Tamada, Masateru Tsunoda, and Ken-ichi Matsumoto, “Using Software Birthmarks to Identify Similar Classes and Major Functionalities,” In Proc.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
