<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>github on Haruaki TAMADA</title>
    <link>https://tamada.github.io/tags/github/</link>
    <description>Recent content in github on Haruaki TAMADA</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tamada.github.io/tags/github/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Git/GitHub Operation Support for Novice Programmers</title>
      <link>https://tamada.github.io/research/git_operation_supports/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tamada.github.io/research/git_operation_supports/</guid>
      <description>:speaking_head: Overview Learning the git and GitHub operation is difficult for novice programmers. Since even programming is a pretty complicated task, it becomes challenging to consider various kinds of operation except programming, for example, good commit, pull requests, and etc. However, the recent development process ordinary manages product versions with SCM such as git. Therefore, it requires the novices should learn them as soon as possible.
Then, we focus on the commits&amp;rsquo; timing, and the proposed system recommends commit at the suitable timing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project as a City</title>
      <link>https://tamada.github.io/research/project_as_a_city/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tamada.github.io/research/project_as_a_city/</guid>
      <description>:speaking_head: Overview Social coding platforms (SCPs) have realized spontaneous software evolution, where new source code and ideas are spontaneously proposed by altruistic developers. Although there are many projects operated by active communities performing spontaneous evolution, it is yet unclear that how such successful projects and communities have been formed and governed. In this paper, we propose a method that can investigate the history of every project in the SCP. Introducing the concept of project as a city, we consider every project in the SCP as a city, where a government and citizens develop a city through collaborative activities.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
